An Inventory of the Republican National Committee (U.S.) Opposition Research Group records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Geraldine Ferraro materials, 1978-1984 (Box 39-45)
  - John Zaccaro materials, 1978-1984 (Folder 45:38)
    Includes materials regarding building code violations and other legal and financial documents
  - Financial information, 1977-1983 (Folder 39)
    - Ferraro/Zaccaro tax and disclosure statements, 1977-1983 (Folder 39: 17-18)
- John Glenn materials, 1961-1984 (Box 46-55)
  Comprised of candidate notebooks, which contain photocopies of clippings and other materials related to his political career, and related documents.
  - Candidate notebooks, 1979-1984 (Folder 46-55)
    - 1984 March (Folder 46: 1-2)
    - 1984 March (Folder 55: 8)
    - 1984 February (Folder 46: 3-7)
    - 1984 February (Folder 47: 1-6)
    - 1984 February (Folder 55: 6-7)
    - 1984 January (Folder 48: 1-7)
    - 1984 January (Folder 55: 5)
    - 1983 December 19-31 (Folder 49: 1)
    - 1983 December 11-18 (Folder 49: 2)
    - 1983 December 6-10 (Folder 49: 3)
    - 1983 December 1-6 (Folder 49: 4)
    - 1983 December (Folder 55: 4)
    - 1983 November 21-30 (Folder 49: 5)
    - 1983 November 15-20 (Folder 49: 6)
    - 1983 November 1-14 (Folder 49: 7)
    - 1983 November (Folder 49: 8)
    - 1983 October 15-31 (Folder 50: 1)
    - 1983 October 8-14 (Folder 50: 2)
    - 1983 October 1-7 (Folder 50: 3)
    - 1983 October (Folder 55: 3)
    - 1983 October, Miscellany (Folder 50: 4)
    - 1983 September 18-30 (Folder 50: 5)
    - 1983 September 12-16 (Folder 50: 6)
    - 1983 September 1-11 (Folder 50: 7)
    - 1983 August 20-31 (Folder 50: 8)
    - 1983 August 1-19 (Folder 51: 1)
    - 1983 July 20-31 (Folder 51: 2)
    - 1983 July 10-19 (Folder 51: 3)
    - 1983 July 1-9 (Folder 51: 4)
    - 1983 June 14-30 (Folder 51: 5)
    - 1983 June 1-13 (Folder 51: 6)
    - 1983 June (Folder 55: 2)
    - 1983 May 18-31 (Folder 52: 1)
    - 1983 May 1-18 (Folder 52: 2)
    - 1983 April 22-30 (Folder 52: 3)
    - 1983 April 1-21 (Folder 52: 4)
    - 1983 March 20-31 (Folder 52: 5)
    - 1983 March 11-20 (Folder 52: 6)
    - 1983 March 1-10 (Folder 52: 7)
    - 1983 February 18-28 (Folder 52: 8)
    - 1983 February 8-17 (Folder 52: 9)
    - 1983 February 1-7 (Folder 52: 10)
    - 1983 February (Folder 55: 1)
    - 1983 January 17-31 (Folder 53: 1)
    - 1983 January 11-16 (Folder 53: 2)
    - 1983 January 1-10 (Folder 53: 3)
    - 1982 August 1-December 28 (Folder 53: 4)
    - 1982 May 4-July 18 (Folder 53: 5)
    - 1982 January 17-April 25 (Folder 53: 6)
    - 1981 July 14-December (Folder 53: 7)
    - 1981 January-June 29 (Folder 53: 8)
    - 1980 January 12-December 12 (Folder 53: 9)
    - 1979 January 16-December 22 (Folder 54: 1)
    - 1978 January 18-December 18 (Folder 54: 2)
    - 1975 January 12-December 15 (Folder 54: 3)
    - 1974 August 7-December 19 (Folder 54: 4)
    - 1974 January 6-July 31 (Folder 54: 5)
    - 1961 December 11-December 15 1973 (Folder 54: 6)
- Republican National Committee (RNC) Records, 1984 (Box 56-58)
  Includes correspondence, reports, memoranda, and material regarding the Voices for Victory media campaign.
  - External correspondence, 1984 (Folder 56: 1)
  - Internal correspondence and memoranda, 1984 (Folder 56: 2-4)
  - Michael J. Bayer pre-Convention (Democratic) memoranda, 1984 (Folder 56: 5)
  - Michael J. Bayer Convention (Democratic) memoranda, 1984 (Folder 56: 6)
  - Eddie Mahe, Jr. memoranda, 1984 (Folder 56: 7)
  - Miscellaneous press clippings, 1984 (Folder 56: 8)
  - Notes, 1984 (Folder 56: 9)
  - Office records and collected items, 1984 (Folder 56: 10-11, Folder 57: 1)
  - Voices for Victory related documents, 1984 (Folder 57)
    - Manuals and overview, 1984 (Folder 57: 2)
    - Messages, 1984 (Folder 57: 3-4)
    - Status reports, 1984 September-October (Folder 57: 5-7)
    - Miscellaneous reports, 1984 (Folder 57: 8-9, Folder 58: 1-2)
    - Bound report of multiple activities, 1984 November (Folder 58)
- General Democratic Party research materials, 1983-1984 (Box 59-60)
  Consists of documents on Democratic Party platforms, including general party information. See also Audiovisual file for party debates.
  - American for Democratic Candidates, "Democratic Candidates' Issue Position and Voting Records,", 1983 September 23 (Folder 59:1)
  - Cranston, Alan related documents, circa 1984 (Folder 59:2)
  - Democratic National Committee workshops, 1984 (Folder 59:3)
  - Individual campaign literature, 1984 (Folder 59:4)
  - Party platforms analysis, 1984 (Folder 59:5)
  - Party Platforms, 1984 (Folder 59-60)
    - Asia, 1984 (Folder 59: 6)
    - Blacks, 1984 (Folder 59: 7)
    - Business/economics, 1984 (Folder 59: 8)
    - Central America, 1984 (Folder 59: 9)
    - Convention information, 1984 (Folder 59: 10)
    - Defense budget, 1984 (Folder 60: 1)
    - Disabled people, 1984 (Folder 60: 2)
    - Environment/pollution, 1984 (Folder 60: 3)
    - Individual campaign literature, 1984 (Folder 60: 4)
    - Israel/Middle East, 1984 (Folder 60: 5)
    - Nuclear weapons, 1984 (Folder 60: 6)
    - Religious/peace group, 1984 (Folder 60: 7)
    - Torture/human rights, 1984 (Folder 60: 8)
    - Women's issues, 1984 (Folder 60: 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Folder 60: 10)
- Debates file, 1983-1984 (Box 61-62)
  Comprised of material directly regarding the presidential and vice-presidential debates. Includes correspondence and memoranda directly referencing the debates and information regarding mock-debates for Ronald Reagan and George H.W. Bush. See also Audiovisual file.
  - Presidential debates, 1983-1984 (Folder 61)
    - Debate transcripts, 1984 (Folder 61: 1-2)
    - First Presidential debate analysis, 1984 (Folder 61: 3)
    - Second Presidential debate analysis, 1984 (Folder 61: 4)
    - General Presidential debate analysis, 1984 (Folder 61: 5)
    - Presidential debates related materials, 1983-1984 (Folder 61: 6-7)
  - Vice-Presidential debates, 1984 (Folder 62)
    - Bush-Ferraro debate briefing book, 1984 (Folder 62: 1)
    - Debate preparation documents, 1984 (Folder 62: 2)
    - Vice-presidential debate related materials, 1984 (Folder 62: 3)
- Special interest groups file, 1981-1984, undated (Box 62-63)
  Consists of clippings and related documents on specific organizations and groups that appeared to favor the Democratic Party.
  - Americans for Democratic Action (ADA), 1983-1984 (Folder 62: 4)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), circa 1983-1984 (Folder 62: 5-6)
  - Gay rights, circa 1983-1984 (Folder 63: 1)
  - League of Conservation voters, 1984 (Folder 63: 2)
  - Gertrude Stein Democratic Club, 1981-1984 (Folder 63: 3)
  - National Association of Social Workers, 1981 (Folder 63: 4)
  - National Education Association (NEA), circa 1983-1984 (Folder 63: 5)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW), circa 1983-1984 (Folder 63: 6)
  - United Mine Workers, 1983-1984 (Folder 63: 7)
- Subject file, 1980-1984 (Box 63-64)
  Includes material on specific special interest groups and other documents and materials collected by the RNC.
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, Power and Principle excerpt, 1983 (Folder 63: 8)
    Photocopies from book
  - Cytowic, Richard E., "Health to the Chief: the Politics of Ageing[sic] and Illness,", 1984 August 16 (Folder 63: 9)
  - Federal Election Commission records, Democratic Party candidates, 1982 (Folder 64: 1)
  - Federal Election Commission records, 1983-1984 (Folder 64: 2)
  - Republican National Committee Public Affairs Department, "The Carter Record,", 1980 August (Folder 64: 3)
  - Transcript of presentation with at least one unidentified speaker, 1984 July 6 (Folder 64: 4)
- Sound Recordings, 1978; 1984 (Box 65)
  Contains sound recordings of speeches given by Geraldine Ferraro in 1978, as well as campaign speeches of Geraldine Ferraro and Walter Mondale in 1984.
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - FER 107 (Cassette), 1978 October 16 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - FER 109 (Cassette), 1978 November 2 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - Holy Child - FER 104B (Cassette), 1978 October 9 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - Richmond Hill Block Assoc. - FER 108 (Cassette), 1978 October 31 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - St Francis & Ridgeway Prop. - FER 102 (Cassette), 1978 October 5 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - St Stadislan - FER 106 (Cassette), 1978 October 25 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - Lionel Club Rich/Hill - FER 105 (Cassette), 1978 October 24 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - Miraculous Medal - FER 100 (Cassette), 1978 October 10 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - Woodhaven Res. Block Assoc. FER 103 (Cassette), 1978 October 18 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - Holy Child FER 104A (Cassette), 1978 October 9 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - Jackson Heights Comm. Center - FER 110 (Cassette), 1978 October 19 (Folder 65)
  - "Delibovi vs Ferraro" - Glendale Taxpayers Asso. FER 101 (Cassette), 1978 October 5 (Folder 65)
  - Ferraro Tax Briefing (Cassette), 1984 October 20 (Folder 65)
  - Ferraro Financial Briefing (2 Cassettes), 1984 August 21 (Folder 65)
  - Ferraro News Conference (3 Cassettes), 1984 August 21 (Folder 65)
  - Ferraro - Vicount Hotel - JFK Airport (Cassette), 1984 August 21 (Folder 65)
- Floppy disks, 1984 June (Box 65)
  - Mondale (3 5.5" computer floppy disks), 1984 June (Folder 65)
- Video tapes, 1976-1984 (Box 65-66)
  Contains video recordings of speeches given by Walter Mondale and Geraldine Ferraro while campaigning for the presidency in 1984 as well as earlier speeches. Footage of the presidential and vice presidential debates is also included.
  - Democratic Debate, Manchester (2 U-Matic tapes), 1984 February 23 (Folder 65)
  - Democratic Debate, Atlanta (U-Matic tape), 1984 March 11 (Folder 65)
  - Democratic Debate, Chicago, partial (VHS), 1984 March 18 (Folder 65)
  - Democratic Debate, Chicago, partial (U-Matic tape), 1984 March 18 (Folder 65)
  - First Ford-Carter Debate (2 U-Matic tapes), 1976 September 23 (Folder 65)
  - PBS Republican Forum (2 U-Matic tapes), 1980 March 13 (Folder 65)
  - Vice-Presidential Debate (2 U-Matic tapes), 1984 September 10 (Folder 65)
  - Democratic Debate, Hanover, NH (U-Matic tape), 1984 January 15 (Folder 66)
  - Democratic Candidates Debate - Pittsburgh, PA - CNN (U-Matic tape), 1984 April 5 (Folder 66)
  - Martin/Bayer (Ferraro/Bush) - Mock Debate (VHS), 1984 September 27 (Folder 66)
  - Malaise: Twenty Years of Walter Mondale - Master (U-Matic tape), circa 1980 (Folder 66)
  - Ferraro Video (U-Matic tape), undated (Folder 66)
  - Ferraro - Master Edit (U-Matic tape), undated (Folder 66)
  - Democratic Debate, Des Moines, Iowa (2 U-Matic tapes), 1984 February 11 (Folder 66)
  - Republican Debate - Reagan v. Bush - PBS (U-Matic tapes), circa 1980s (Folder 66)
  - Danforth-Woods - 1st Debate (U-Matic tapes), 1982 October 21 (Folder 66)
  - Danforth-Woods - 2nd Debate (U-Matic tapes), 1982 October 22 (Folder 66)